Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
No!
So strong!
What kind of magic is this?
Now, how should you die?
Please! Please spare us! We'll never attack another village again! I swear!
Maybe I won't kill you this time.
Huh?
Since it is a special day.
The day that an angel was born.
Go on. I want to hear you wish her a happy birthday.
Who is that?
Celebrate her with every fiber of your being, before you die.
So you are gonna kill us!
they were gonna kill us, bro?
Thank you.
Knowing him, he's being reckless and getting into all kinds of trouble.
But it's all right!
You can come home any time, Asta!
Let's see.
He says, dear sister, fellow church orphans, and Hajj village chief.
What am I, shop liver?
Asta's made it to junior magic knight third class!
What?
Good job, Asta.
Glad you're not slacking off.
I knew you could do it, Asta!
You boys take care of yourselves and keep doing us proud, you hear?
You know, I've heard that you've been promoted to magic knight first class.
Congratulations!
It's not really a big deal.
Exactly right.
We can't have you getting a big head.
Never forget that I am your better in both rank and experience.
Is everything all right, sir?
Take it.
A promotion gift from your superior.
You keep that for yourself.
I know where all your earnings go.
He doesn't always know how to express his emotions.
I wish you'd gotten to see it, though.
He was so happy when he heard about your promotion.
I think his glasses were sparkling.
That's pathetic.
All right, I need everyone to listen up.
Our wages have come in, so there's no work today.
Yeah!
Okay, time to get training!
Yummy, sir!
Thank you!
Great call as usual!
Time for a drink!
Or three!
Well, you know what that calls for?
Check it!
All right, it's time to get busy!
Ladies, hey there!
Who's your guy?
Me!
Oh, yeah, Ghosh.
That bandit thing yesterday?
Good job.
Today is my little sister Marie's birthday.
Do you think I could extend my time off until her next birthday?
Hell no.
Free time?
Man, I hope somebody attacks the capital again!
Oh, hey!
Maybe I should do it!
That's an even bigger no.
I guess nobody feels like working.
Hey!
Kat's creation magic!
Feed me, sheep cook!
Stuffed my face!
Yeah!
Hot potatoes!
No way!
They're a specialty of ours village!
That's where my darling friendship for visitors is from!
Give it my try!
So good!
Thank you!
They're pretty dense.
Must be really high in fiber.
Oh, it's super crumbly!
Amazing how it sucks out of moisture out of your mouth.
These would make for a pretty good bar snack.
Sure!
What present would be a worthy tribute to my little goddess on her birthday?
It's time.
Ladies of the Clover Kingdom, get ready.
Here comes...
Wait!
Oh, right, of course.
You'll be wanting me to take you into town for another match, huh, Captain?
Yep.
But first...
All that fiber must have kicked in.
I might push past my limits right here.
That's one limit you do not need to push past, sir!
So gross!
What now?
I get a day off out of nowhere and there's nothing to do.
Magnus, sir!
Hmm?
Sorry to bother you, sir!
But if you have time, will you please take me somewhere on your awesome broom?
Oh?
How can I say no when you ask how sweet and polite like that, Rasta?
Where to?
Neon, sir!
Wait!
I know that place!
It's where the boys went for that stupid mixer!
Sure.
So, what you going there for?
Well, uh...
Well, what?
I think we could talk on the way.
Oh, come on!
Not that I care what he does!
Or who he may or may not be going to see!
It's simple curiosity, that's all!
Well, are you coming?
What?
Like, now?
Now or never, it's your call, dude.
Now is good!
Get ready and hold on tight!
Huh?
Oh, yeah!
Okay, so maybe I do care!
Greetings, my darling sister Marie.
I've just arrived in the village where you live.
Let's get out of here.
Being a magic knight isn't easy.
But I don't mind because I'm doing it for you.
And with my wages, I can buy you the presents you deserve.
Me, a former prisoner, living a life on the straight and narrow?
It's thanks to you, Marie, my angel-made flesh.
I do it for you.
My nose won't stop bleeding.
Gosh, sir!
We've been waiting for you.
If you would please step inside, we have presents ready for your perusal.
Show me immediately.
Right away!
First up, these!
Perfect for a little girl.
They all just love stuffed animals.
One of these would be sure to put a smile on her face.
They're perfect.
Thanks so much.
Yes, I'll take them all.
Certainly, sir.
Our next item.
She'll be playing with us for hours, imagining herself living in such a place.
A perfect home she'd share with her brother, naturally.
Big brother!
I'm so glad you're home!
I'll take that, too.
Excellent, sir!
Last but not least, with this costume, your sister can be a real angel.
You know, Gosh.
I love you.
The whole store, I want it all.
Always a pleasure, sir.
What?
You're visiting some girl you met at a mixer?
Sure am.
I promised Rebecca I'd come play with her brothers and sisters sometime.
Go, Asta.
You're a fast mover, already bringing the whole family in on your date.
I'm proud of you, buddy.
Yeah!
Hey, look, Neon's up ahead.
All right!
I'm going to play so hard, they won't know what hit them!
Oh, take it easy, boy.
All right!
Greetings, my beloved little sister Marie.
Please forgive your brother whose blood loss has made him tardy.
I've brought you so many birthday presents.
I hope they will bring you great joy.
All my wages are gone now, but no price is too high for your happiness.
Soon I'll see my precious angel again.
And that smiling face of hers.
Ah, my darling Marie.
Marie.
You like that, huh, Marie?
So fun!
You're really strong, Asta!
I want to turn!
Me too!
Okay, come on and...
Ah!
Get away from her right now, you scum!
Oh, it's the Bloody Nose Sister Lover!
Call me a Bloody Nose Sister Lover again, Meathead.
I'll squash you!
That isn't going to happen!
Not the way I've been training!
Shut up!
I only get to see my sister once a month, which means these visits are sacrosanct.
Today I set aside all of their thoughts, ready to dote on my Marie in every way possible.
It was supposed to be flirty and fun and perfect!
So how is it that you showed up here before me?
So you do have a sister complex and get nosebleeds.
And how was I supposed to know she was your sister?
Stop pointing your grubby little finger at my angel!
I know I showed you her picture, don't lie!
Did you?
I don't remember.
I met her today when I came over to Rebecca's to play with her brothers and sisters.
Uh, hi.
He's really scary.
What's flirty, Meathead?
I don't know that word.
Shh!
Well, Marie's cute, that's for sure.
Of course she's cute, but that doesn't mean you have permission to make eyes at my sister,
you filth!
Stop it, brother!
I don't want you doing mean things to him!
Please, Osta's going to be my husband someday!
Osta's going to be my husband someday!
Her husband!
When I tagged along with them, that was not what I was expecting!
Uh, the fair, miss?
Will this be enough?
Heck yeah!
Kill.
You okay?
Kill now!
Mirror magic!
Reflect ray!
Hey, what are you doing with that mirror?
Now die.
Whoa!
Please stop!
Don't hurt him!
Oh my.
It's awfully noisy out here.
Marie, it's time to go.
You need to get back to the church now.
Sister.
I see.
So you're here, Ghosh.
That's right, Hag.
That's sister to you.
Mind your manners.
Marie and I are going on a date.
You can head back to the church on your own.
No, Ghosh.
She's coming.
The sooner you accept that, the better for us all.
When are you going to realize that you're no good for an impressionable young girl like
Marie?
She deserves to be around somebody better than you, with your bad attitude and nasty tongue.
What was that, you old croon?
There, see?
Just dropped dead.
A nice thing to say to an old woman nearing the end of her life, thoughtless fool.
Says the demon witch who'll live for another hundred years, or two, or three.
Only a thug would resort to that sort of name calling.
Shut up, you worthless bag.
Hold on a sec.
You can't just talk to an elderly woman of the clump like that.
It's just wrong.
Nobody asked you to get involved.
Now back off.
Just go home.
Come along now, Marie.
Bye, Ghosh.
Bye, Asta.
I had fun.
No.
Marie.
Bye, Marie.
Hey, are you going to be okay?
Marie.
He's really weird.
You hungry?
We could go and grab some food at the restaurant while your night friend recovers.
You could, um, stay the night at our place if you want.
You mean it?
Uh, hey, hey!
Spend the night?
Are you kidding?
Sleeping at the house of a woman he just met?
That's madness.
Madness!
Oh, I had a great time today.
Asta's really funny.
The obnoxiously loud boy?
Yeah!
Oh, yeah!
Have some more.
Here, would you like some moguro berries, birdie?
Whoa.
Man, every bite I take is better than the last one.
Really?
Thank you.
Yeah, you know, you'd make a great wife with these cooking skills.
I wasn't going for that.
This is ridiculous.
Cooking skills aren't the only thing that makes someone a good wife.
Yes!
Hey, sis.
Are you going to marry Asta someday?
No!
Why would you say that?
Yeah, right!
Over my dead body!
So, sis, are you going to make a move while he's here?
No!
Where did that come from, Luca?
Pam?
You too?
I don't need all of you ganging up on me.
Make a move on him?
No, that would just be crazy.
I never thought I would miss Magna's exploding fireball.
Why is it so cold?
It's not even winter.
Huh?
Are you going to make a move while he's here?
Pan, you two?
Stupid, ridiculous, insane.
I would never do anything like that.
I'll just check to make sure Luca and Marco are asleep.
Maybe then I can get some rest.
It's time for you to die.
Mirror magic, reflect Ray.
What the heck is going on here?
Die, Asta.
Who, me?
But why?
I will never allow you to marry Marie.
And there's one foolproof way of preventing it.
Come on, it's just something the kids say.
Also, you jerk, I was a slave.
You can call me whatever you want.
As long as I get to kill you.
Mirror magic, my real double.
Two gauches and mirror shooting death beams?
What's up with this guy's magic anyway?
You have been found guilty of the crime of meeting my little sister.
Are a lot of people guilty of that?
Just shut up and die.
We don't even live here.
What?
There's snow everywhere.
Where did it all come from?
It's not even winter yet.
That's not important right now.
Die!
Hey, stop it.
What are you doing out here?
I'm sorry.
Things got out of hand.
Never mind.
It's the children.
They're missing.
What?
Uriah?
Where are you?
Christopher!
Vaughn is missing too.
I don't know.
No.
How exciting.
I just love making new friends.
Come on now.
Just remember I could change the world
I'm not so sick
If I do never know what it is
I simply smash it
Pleaseutake to it
Let's go
Mom是 on Andrew
It's wonderful
Vise be it
Please sleep
Noooooooooooooooooooo!
Big Brother!
Hm?
Will you sweet me around like Asta?
Swing you around?
Like him?
Are you okay?
I can't bring myself to disappoint her.
I'll just have my clone handle it.
Mirror magic?
My real double!
Now swing her around.
I could never put Maria in any danger.
You're so right!
Let's try this instead.
Here we go, around and around!
Let's see the ABCs of cooking.
All you underlings, bow to my royal magnificence and cower before me.
Black Clover, page 31.
Pursuit over the snow.
Wait, this is no time for word games!
Those children are in danger!
Diamant!
Goolir!
You gun deeper into of canina!
awi!
Mario!
No!
Don't worry!
I'm your athlete!
Huh?
We can't get out on Θ journée about that
he's going through!
Look here, man!